<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Learn - Category - Jiabin&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>https://daijiabin.github.io/categories/learn/</link>
        <description>Learn - Category - Jiabin&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 12:30:06 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://daijiabin.github.io/categories/learn/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>LeetCode</title>
    <link>https://daijiabin.github.io/leetcode/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 12:30:06 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://daijiabin.github.io/leetcode/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Go Through LeetCode Recursion / Binary Tree 112. Path Sum - simple recursion   Discription:
  Given the root of a binary tree and an integer targetSum, return true if the tree has a root-to-leaf path such that adding up all the values along the path equals targetSum.
  A leaf is a node with no children.
    Idea:
  What kind of traverse should we use?]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Algorithms -- Recursion</title>
    <link>https://daijiabin.github.io/algorithms/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 16:51:37 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://daijiabin.github.io/algorithms/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Ideas Recursion  What important is, NEVER JUMP INTO RECURSION.  1. Recursion in List   Figure out what does your Function proceedure with, what kind of value will it return.
  Consider about the Base-Case, with which we can end the recursion
  Deal with the rest part ( beyond the Base-Case ) recursively by using your Function.
  Proceedure the Details of Base-Case.
  1.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Machine Learning</title>
    <link>https://daijiabin.github.io/machine-learning/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 19:11:53 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://daijiabin.github.io/machine-learning/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Lecture by Andrew Ng, Coursera Basic Concepts &amp; Linear Regression Supervised Learning vs. Unsupervised Learning   Supervised Learning:
 In supervised learning, we are given a data set and already know what our correct output should look like, having the idea that there is a relationship between the input and the output.
   Training Data already has the value, which our Function should predict for a new, strange input.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
