<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>TUD - Category - Jiabin&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>https://daijiabin.github.io/categories/tud/</link>
        <description>TUD - Category - Jiabin&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 09:13:09 &#43;0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://daijiabin.github.io/categories/tud/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>ASiSE 03. ADED</title>
    <link>https://daijiabin.github.io/asise/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 09:13:09 &#43;0200</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://daijiabin.github.io/asise/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is ADED  A nalyse  rol3: existing technologies, backgrounds, problems   D esign  rol3: new technologies   E valuate  necessary for technical papers a technical thesis must be technical( achieve and demonstrate a technical result ) success factors have to be analyzed to know whether a result is really needed rol3: show why the new solution is superior; use success cretiria   D iffuse  by writing: a design pattern, a report by demonstrating a software prototype rol3: popularize the research results; demonstration for creating vision    Tasks for each    Analyse Design Evaluate(Role?]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Note2021</title>
    <link>https://daijiabin.github.io/note2021/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 17:19:52 &#43;0200</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://daijiabin.github.io/note2021/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Try to write some Notes here  Not FREE.   Two threads will never enter the critical section at the same time(mutual exclusion) - safety If two threads try to enter critical section, eventually one of them will succeed - Liveness  ]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Haupt Seminar</title>
    <link>https://daijiabin.github.io/haupt-seminar/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 16:38:33 &#43;0200</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://daijiabin.github.io/haupt-seminar/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Some Definitions Network Edge  Where devices or local network interfaces with Internet  Fog/Edge/Mobile-Edge Computing   Fog/Edge Computing is a distributed computing paradigm that brings data storage and computation closer to where it is needed to improve the response time and save bandwidth.
  Mobile Edge Computing is a network archietecture which enables the cloud computing capabilities and IT services at the edge of the network.
  Software-Defined-Network   Features:]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>2021 Sose</title>
    <link>https://daijiabin.github.io/2021-sose/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 13:24:13 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://daijiabin.github.io/2021-sose/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Kurs Katalog Sommersemester 2021 INF-BAS3 Software- und Web-Engineering   Component-based Software Engineering (2/2/0)
  Internet and Web Applications (2/2/0)
  Software Fault Tolerance (2/2/0)
  Softwaremanagement (2/2/0)
  Spatiotemporal Modeling and Simulation of Biological Systems (2/2/0)
  INF-BAS4 Systemarchitektur   Internet and Web Applications (2/2/0)
  Software Fault Tolerance (2/2/0)
  Distributed Operating Systems (2/1/0)
  Wireless Sensor Networks (2/2/0)]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
